umbler.com 2019-07-21

# Privacy Policy | Umbler | Umbler

### Privacy Policy

November 19th, 2018

Attention: All aspects of the Usage and Privacy Policies and the Terms of Service are available in Brazilian Portuguese. Any translated material that you may receive will be for convenience only. If there is any conflict between the Brazilian Portuguese and the translated version, the Brazilian Portuguese version will prevail. 

> Umbler ("Umbler" or "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of the individuals visiting the company's websites ("visitors") and individuals who register to use the Services (APP), as defined below ("Customers "). This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices in connection with the use of the Company's websites and the related applications and services offered by Umbler (the "Services").

#### 1\. Websites

This Privacy Policy covers the information on the websites that point to this Privacy Policy, including https://umbler.com (referred to as "Umbler Sites" or "Company Sites"). Websites hosted on the Umbler Service are created and managed by Umbler customers. These websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. 

Umbler allows its customers to use third-party services (referred to as "add-ons") as part of running Web applications on the Company platform. When you share information with these add-ons, the Privacy Policy that applies is the one of the Add-on Provider. Umbler sites may contain links to other sites. The practices or content of such other information sites is governed by the privacy statements of those other websites.

#### 2\. Collected Information

By expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the services or registering to use the Services, Umbler may require you to provide the Company with personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, telephone number and e-mail ("Required Contact Information"). When purchasing the Services, Umbler requires that you provide us with billing information, such as your name as it is on your credit card, billing address, and credit card number ("Billing Information"). Umbler may also ask you to provide additional information. Mandatory contact information, billing information, and optional customer information are collectively referred to as "Umbler Customer Data." 

As you browse the Company's website, Umbler may also collect information through the use of tools in the collection of information, such as cookies. The navigation information includes standard information for your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), Internet Protocol ("IP"), and actions you take on Company websites (such as visited and clicked links).

#### 3\. Use of Collected Information

The Company uses Umbler’s Customer Data to perform the requested services. For example, if you fill out a "Send a Message" contact form, the Company will use the information you provide to contact you about your interest in the Services. In addition, customers may choose to invite a friend to use Umbler Services in a collaborative way (referred to as addition of "collaborators"). Umbler should receive your friend's email address, and send the friend an invitation email.

The Company may also use Umbler’s Customer Data for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use the information you provide to contact you to discuss your interest in the services and to send you information about the Company and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

Umbler uses credit card information only to receive payment for the Services.

Umbler uses Navigation Information to operate and improve the company's website. The Company may also use Shipping Information alone or in combination with Umbler Customer Data to provide personalized information about the company.

#### 4\. Website’s Navigation Information

Cookies, web beacons and IP adresses.

Umbler uses information gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect information such as browsing the Company's websites ("website navigation information"). This section describes the types of website navigation information that may be collected on the Company's websites and how such information may be used. 

#### 5\. Customer Testimonials

Umbler may use testimonials on the company websites that contain information such as customer names and titles. Umbler obtains the consent of each Client before publishing any testimony.

#### 6\. Communication Preferences

Umbler provides Customers and Visitors who provide contact information with means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You can manage to receive non-transactional marketing communications by clicking the "unsubscribe" link located at the bottom of the Company's marketing emails. In addition, you can submit a request specifying your communication preferences to friends@umbler.com. Customers can not opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account with Umbler or the Services.

#### 7\. Correction and Update of your Information

Customers can update or change their registration information by editing their data through the "Profile" page. Requests to access, change or delete information will be processed within 30 (thirty) days.

#### 8\. Data Storage

Umbler stores the received information as described in this Privacy Policy above for a reasonable length of time, for example, as the case may be, for as long as is necessary to provide our Services, comply with our legal obligations, solve disputes, establish legal defenses, to conduct audits and enforce our agreements.

#### 9\. Customer Data

As part of our use of our services, customers may submit the electronic data or information to the Services ("Customer Data"), which may include personal information. The Company generally has no direct relationship to the persons to whom the customer data may relate, which we process on behalf of our customers. If personal information that belongs to you as an individual has been sent to us by a customer as customer data and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to correct, change or delete such data, please inquire with the customer (or his / her organization) directly.

#### 10\. Security

Umbler uses administrative, technical, physical, and appropriate security measures to protect the Umbler Customer Data.

#### 11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Umbler reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Umbler will provide notice of material changes to this Privacy Policy through Company websites at least fifteen (15) days before the changes take effect.

#### 12\. How to contact us

Issues related to this Company Privacy Policy should be directed to abuse@umbler.com.

**This document is an adaptation of the Terms of Service of Google App Engine. The original work has been modified. Google Inc. has no connection and does not sponsor or endorse Umbler or its use.**
